In 2026
If you're still using prompts to remove the AI flavor from your articles
you might still be stuck in the 1.0 phase of writing
I believe the most effective way to solve this problem currently
the most effective method is to establish a skill
As for me here,
Recently, I built one for myself that can continuously learn
a skill for my writing style
As I feed it more samples
increasingly such a situation
The articles it produces will increasingly resemble my own style
Unlike the past when we used prompts to solve this problem
This set of skills
It is actually more like a writing manual tailored specifically to your personal style
such a writing handbook
Within this, you can record some of your expression preferences
writing habits
banned words and style boundaries, etc.
and you can continuously make updates
Before each writing task, the AI will refer to this manual of yours.
Previously, we used prompts to address this issue
what is it actually more like
It's like we temporarily assign to a new employee
to communicate some of our company's regulations
So this 'skill' here
It actually functions more like a
a handbook we wrote for new employees' onboarding
Each time, we just need to let the AI review our manual first
and then proceed with the task
Moreover, every time you identify where it is most prone to making mistakes
then you can correct it in this way
add this piece in
used over time
This onboarding manual will become increasingly accurate
The AI will also understand better
what you write
it will increasingly align with your personal style
So how exactly do you implement the method I mentioned above?
I've broken it down into four steps.
First, there is a prerequisite
you need to install Cloud Code properly
If you don't know how to install it
I will provide my detailed installation guide here
As for the materials related to today's video
I can release it
You can leave a comment to get it
The first step is
You need to let the AI understand your writing preferences first
then you need to find 3 to 5
your most satisfactory
your original articles
Note that
this must be something you wrote by yourself
rather than being written by AI for you
Then after you have these articles
you send it to cloud code
have it analyze your writing style for you
Then it will list out these elements point by point as 1, 2, 3, 4.
Then what?
At this point
you can have cloud code help you
first generate a published writing style skill
In this regard, it is recommended that you also install this skill
Creator
Regarding this skill
I've also included it in our manual.
This skill can be tailored to your specific needs
a tool to help you create skills
You can see that I've invoked the skill here
help me draft a relatively basic version of this skill
which includes some basic principles and conditions
Of course, please note that the output at this stage is not the final version.
It's just a very rough version
This is just the starting point
If you want to make this skill effective
it must be through your repeated practice
continuously iterate and optimize it
Now, this first step
We have created this skill
Then in the second step
we'll have it follow the requirements in our skill
write a draft according to these requirements
and then you make revisions
For example, we give it a topic like this
Okay
first run 100
Then write this article
You will definitely find some issues more or less
The most crucial step is
You now need to focus on the content it has output
make a word-by-word revision
into the version you're most satisfied with
the revised version of this article
and the version written by AI
don't let it make a comparison
You can provide this set of prompts to it
let it identify the gaps
And then
the AI will recognize your preferences
what kind of expression style it tends to favor
what kind of expression style is disliked
Through such a specific case,
he can more accurately capture some key information
This is also the most valuable part.
This whole system isn't something you do just once and it's over, okay?
You can update it like this every time you write a new piece.
Now, everyone should pay attention here
So if you want to create such a writing
skill
there must be several essential files included
What are the several files I recommend everyone to design?
The first essential component must be the skill dot
MD is an essential file
In this section, regarding the composition of prompts
You can start from these aspects
If you have any additional reference materials
such as commonly used terminology
fixed expressions and so on
You can add a new file
through a reference file
in here
you can include your relevant reference materials in it
If there are any specific requirements for the file format
You can write a script
that is our script
what I just mentioned
You don't actually need to get everything done perfectly at once
Because you'll find that
during this process
where there is an issue
we optimize that specific part
Moreover, the set of skills we've developed above
not just for writing articles
you can actually apply it to other scenarios
for application
For example, if you input a rough piece of voice-over
then let AI help you polish it
Can you then invoke this skill
let it read your past preferences and style
Based on this foundation, proceed with polishing
There are many such scenarios
For example, if you come across some great podcasts
Then you draft an initial version in your own style
then let the AI process it according to your set of skills
the content you personally wrote
organize it into a tutorial-style article
You can directly publish it with one click
So this set of skills
In fact, it can be applied to any writing scenario.
Because this aspect
It contains your personal writing flavor. Okay
That's all for today's content.
So if you're interested in AI-powered content creation
if you're interested in this systematic process
It contains detailed product introductions
If you find today's video helpful,
You can give it a Triple Combo
OK, see you in the next video
Bye